<resources>
    <string name="app_name">TheGreenlight</string>
    <string name="homepage">"Welcome to Hollywood, kid! You made it. You're a big shot producer now. Sure, Hollywood's biased, but that's why we need you. You're about to greenlight the biggest blockbusters of the season!"</string>
    <string name="family_ink">"Kyra’s parents are the owners of a famous tattoo shop who have raised her to one day take over the family business. She’s a talented artist, but there’s just one problem: she HATES needles. A charming coming of age story about how parents just don’t understand."</string>
    <string name="carry_that_weight">"The people of Macomb, Michigan needed a way to raise funds to save their local hospital. When Abigail discovered the National Women’s Weightlifting Competition had quite the grand prize, she knew what the women in her town had to do. Turns out, the women gained more than just muscle...they gained stronger hearts."</string>
    <string name="paranormal_paralegal">"Jacob Emery and Natalie Pearson are your average legal partners...with a side interest in the afterlife. When a widow in town gets wind of their side project, she contacts the team to help her locate the will of her recently deceased husband. The situation surrounding his death turns out to be more complicated than it appears."</string>
    <string name="miranda_priestess">"Miranda was notorious in her small town for being something of a kook, putting in long hours at the herbal shop she ran. But when a dark and mysterious plague descends upon the people in her village, Miranda must summon the powers she didn’t know she had to save her town as she knows it." </string>
    <string name="escape_woods">"Karen, Grace, Jack, and Will, four teens from different walks of life, reluctantly head out to wilderness camp by their parents’ request. After a wrong turn on the trail, these four get separated from their camp leaders and must use their skills to survive on their own. This wasn’t the summer they signed up for."</string>
    <string name="war_on_time">"A group of Airforce Service Pilots during WWII attempt to restore a faulty aircraft only to find that the plane is able to move through time. The women end up traveling decades into the future, only to discover an utterly dystopian end to the war. These pilots need to stop the future from happening in this thrilling and haunting scifi adventure."</string>
    <string name="angel_investors">"The team of financial consultants at InfoCorp can tackle any challenge that comes their way, even if it means breaking a few rules. While crunching numbers one day, the team realizes that they could easily pull a heist on one of their biggest clients. These women just couldn’t pass up the opportunity. Buckle up for thrills, stick-ups, and income statements."</string>
    <string name="software_sky">"This biopic centers on Margaret Hamilton, the inventor of software engineering. Hamilton's innovations go beyond the feats of playing a crucial role in getting humans to the moon, though. Hamilton, along with many other female engineers alike, challenged the male dominated technology field of their time, paving the way for women in science."</string>
    <string name="coney_island">"Before there was Baywatch, there were the Coney Island Six. This thrilling tale exposes how the original lifeguards at New York’s iconic beach came to be. Get ready for a rough, choppy, and lifesaving ride."</string>
    <string name="winkle_me">"When young Peter received the Winkle™ Robot 3000 for his birthday, he was a little disappointed. The 4000 model had been out for months. But this Winkle™ had a different sort of twinkle. A story about a boy and a his new best friend both learning what it means to go from being a boy to becoming a man."</string>
    <string name="caught_in_middle">"Gary had never had much luck with women. But when he met Holly and Vanessa in the same week, he knew his luck had changed. What could be wrong with dating two women at the same time? Little does Gary know...his two dream women are actually best friends."</string>
    <string name="greatest_mistake">"Gak and Fizzle are BACK with a hot new adventure. When Gak discovers his farts can shoot him across dimensions--the boys think they’re in for a wild ride. Little do they know that their inter-dimensional travel has serious consequences!"</string>
    <string name="vortex">"In the 24th century, computer programmer, Janna, finds the fate of the world in her hands when she discovers a glitch in a piece of the WORLDNET security code. Janna must now keep the Great Evil from destroying the world. Together with a mysterious mentor, Mr. Daniel, and zany fellow programmer, Trevor, she must race against time and evil government agencies to save humanity."</string>
    <string name="win_hard">"Todd Meacham, a brilliant student at Yale University, needs some quick cash to pay his tuition bills. He joins a group of students who, under the leadership of unorthodox professor Terry Jervis, use their math skills to win big in Las Vegas. Seduced by a beautiful teammate and loads of money, Todd learns that the stakes are higher than he ever imagined."</string>
    <string name="meet_jeremy">"Even though Jeremy Thumm has developmental disabilities, he has never thought of himself as disadvantaged, and thanks to his supportive mother, Jeremy leads anything but a restricted life. Whether dominating in the pool as a college swimming star, rescuing stray animals, or making inclusive governmental policy change, Jeremy inspires people with his optimism."</string>
    <string name="bounty_valley">"This epic high fantasy revolves around the fate of humanity when the Galgor Tree, whose location in the Hormung Valley has been lost on civilization for ages, is threatened by powerful forces. Fate has placed the protection of this magical Tree in the hands of an unsuspecting young boy named Asger. A daunting task lies ahead for Asger when he becomes the Protector - to save humanity and discover his own powers for good."</string>
    <string name="life_molecule">"This biographical drama reveals how Watson and Crick made the crucial discovery of the double helix DNA molecule and uncovered life's very code. Find out for yourself what life is really made of."</string>
    <string name="bechdel">"Created by author and illustrator Alison Bechdel, the Bechdel Test sets the laughably low bar for the representation of women in movies.</string>
    <string name="three_criteria">To pass the Bechdel Test, a movie must feature:"\n"1. More than one woman"\n"2. Women talking to each other"\n"3. Women talking to each other about something other than a man"</string>
    <string name="discussion">"Things to consider:"\n"1. How are other identity groups portrayed in films?"\n"2. Who makes these media?"\n"3. Do you think women are fairly portrayed in film?"\n"4. What is the result of poor representation?"\n"5. Is the Bechdel Test fair? Is it important?"</string>
</resources>
